I'm on day two of Ozempic.
I'm on day two of Ozempic and my
confidence is already through the roof.
>> [laughter]
>> This fat girl tried to talk to me. I was
like, "Uh-uh, not no more, bitch."
Them days are over.
>> [laughter]
>> This your lady? Not in a month. She
coming with me, now.
Matter of fact, all you dudes in here,
you got 1 month left with your girl.
>> [laughter]
>> If she chooses them.
With my new body now, I'm not a comedian
no more.
>> [laughter]
>> So, unfortunately, I don't have jokes
tonight.
But, I came here to prepare y'all for
the inevitable apocalypse.
Y'all realize that, right? The world's
ending. Some y'all out here still dating
and moving like there's a country left.
It's over.
Stop. If you're a couple tonight, you
don't got to do it now, but at some
point on the way home, look at the
person with them and be like, "Can I not
survive the apocalypse with them?"
>> [laughter]
>> And if the answer is no, get rid of
them. No hard feelings.
Y'all can make it a couple's activity.
>> [laughter]
>> Gift them with a crossbow and wish them
well, but
you got to survive this thing.
It's some single people in here, too.
Look, ladies, tall men, I know y'all
love them. Useless in the apocalypse.
You can't do nothing with a tall man in
the apoca- You can't hide them nowhere.
Y'all trying to hide from the drones,
this big dummy making eye contact with
them.
>> [laughter]
>> Like, [\h__\h] duck. WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
>> TALL DUDES can't even whisper. Have you
heard a tall dude whisper?
There goes our cover. Great.
Ladies, you need a short king that can
burrow.
>> [cheering]
>> Short kings in the house, you need a
short man that can get low in a pinch.
>> [laughter]
>> He could do a surprise attack. A soldier
stop you, he's searching through your
bug-out bag, guess who went there? Your
short king.
>> [laughter]
>> Jumps out like a Pokémon, stabs him in
the artery.
You need
Your tall king going to get separated.
They're going to take your tall man,
they're going to take him to labor camp.
He's going to have to join the militia.
Your short king coming with you, women
and children. He coming right
>> [laughter]
>> Put a little propeller hat on him, he
good to go.
Right this way, young man. You good.
>> [laughter]
>> Ladies, y'all going to need them short
kings.
And it's not just the women, fellas,
it's us, too. There's no use for a freak
in the apocalypse.
>> [laughter]
>> This girl telling me she a squirter.
[\h__\h] that is irresponsible.
>> [laughter]
>> Resources are scarce.
>> And you have the temerity to SQUIRT ALL
NIGHT?
>> [laughter]
>> WE GOT A HIKE TOMORROW. YOU'RE GOING TO
BE DEHYDRATED.
>> [laughter]
>> Don't look at my canteen. I'm not
sharing.
>> [laughter]
>> You need to treat your [\h__\h] like a
camel's hump.
>> [laughter]
>> And preserve the Lord's liquids. All
right?
What is it? Is it pee? It's sustenance.
And we might
>> [laughter]
>> We might need it.
Put out a fire, you never know.
>> [laughter]
>> That [\h__\h] don't even sound sexy in the
apocalypse, do it? [\h__\h] stay wet. [\h__\h]
stay dripping. Great, now the hounds
have tracked us. Great.
>> [laughter]
>> Great.
You left a trail right to the hideout.
Man, I'm telling y'all.
Red flags won't be red flags in the
apocalypse. The things we don't like now
are going to be valuable assets in the
end times.
Right? My homie told me he going to
break up with his girl because she a
stalker.
I'm like, "Not in the apocalypse. That
[\h__\h] is a tracker."
>> [laughter]
>> You might need your crazy ex. You out
foraging in the woods, you slip and get
lost in the cave. What's that movie, 127
hours?
Guess who going to find you? Your crazy
girl.
>> [laughter]
>> Especially if she think you in the cave
with that [\h__\h] She on her way.
>> [laughter]
>> She on her way. Your healthy girl going
to respect your boundaries, all right?
[\h__\h] my boundaries and come find me.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm going to need that [\h__\h] man. I'm
telling you. Ladies, stop. Let it go.
You look too pretty for the apocalypse.
I'm going to be real. You too high
maintenance. Ladies, let yourself go,
all right? Let that callus on the back
of your foot grow.
You might need it to cut rope. You don't
know.
>> [laughter]
>> Somebody got you bound and tied up. I'm
like, "Babe, GIVE ME YOUR FOOT."
>> [laughter]
>> TOO SUPERFICIAL.
Last one, man. I'm telling you, ladies,
I know y'all love big dicks.
But micro penis No, I'm just kidding.
Y'all need
Micro penises is how we got into this
mess in the first place.
>> [cheering]
[applause]
>> One very particular micro penis.
>> [laughter]
>> Some say the best.
>> [applause]
>> I'm not going to survive the apocalypse,
so I'm dating for what I need right now
in this immediate moment. I'm on the
apps looking for a Filipino nurse.
>> [laughter]
>> Male or female, I don't
>> As long as your pronouns is RN, we good
to go.
Once you identify, can you take vitals?
>> [laughter]
>> Cuz my health care, man, they playing
with my health care.
Try to get Adderall. Well, I couldn't
ever really get Adderall. For those who
don't know, Adderall is a pill that was
invented so that white students can
compete with Asians.
>> [laughter]
>> It's a fact, yeah.
And because of that, they don't really
like to give it to black people.
So,
>> [laughter]
>> I'm glad y'all found that [\h__\h] funny.
It's very inconvenient.
>> [laughter]
>> I want Adderall, I got to meet a kid
named Cooper at a middle school. It's
not
Met up with Cooper, he was saying
because
his parents he was worried one of his
parents get deported. I thought he was
white, turns out he's Wasian.
Y'all know if y'all know what Wasian is,
it's half white and half Asian, so he
technically is Adderall, he don't need
it. You know what I mean? But
>> [laughter]
>> I felt bad, man, cuz right now
immigration, all this [\h__\h] going on in
this country, man, this
that ICE [\h__\h] is evil. I don't care what
side you're on. If you can't see with
your own eyes, ICE is evil, something is
truly [\h__\h] wrong with you.
Like look, I support like I'm never down
No, for real, I don't I'm not doing it
for class, man.
>> [applause]
>> That's how I truly feel, especially here
in California, where we targeting
Mexicans and Latinos. This is native
indigenous land that was stolen from
people, Texas, Arizona, all of that. You
take their land and deny them access to
it. I don't know if you guys know this,
but Chicago has a large thriving Mexican
community. And when I found that out, I
was like, all right, now that's
trespassing. That's
Now, hold on now. You
You had to pass several states to get to
that [\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> Mexicans in Shy-raq?
Snow Mexicans?
>> [laughter]
>> And I'm sorry if that's racist. If it
is, pull me aside, let's have a
dialogue, but [laughter]
the snow is robbing you of a rich
Latino. You can't jump on a bouncy house
in a blizzard. LIKE, WHAT?
>> [applause]
>> DO I THINK EVERY Mexican immigrant here
is a criminal? No. Do I think everyone
in Chicago is? You god damn right. I
DON'T
TRUST WHITE PEOPLE from Chicago.
Listen. You don't need me to know that
you don't belong in Chicago. The city
itself, the way it's spelled, c h i c a
g o, Chico go. Get the [\h__\h] out.
>> [laughter]
>> All this stuff, man, this country is
just mad right now. Everybody was
tripping about Bad Bunny, right, about
his
halftime performance because it wasn't
in English. That was a very beautiful
performance, and I was for real, I was
on his side.
I didn't think he should perform in
English, perform in Spanish. Because as
a performer who travels around a lot and
speaks in English, there's always a
confused white man
with a confused look on his face.
Like, he can't understand the words that
are coming out of my mouth.
There's one here tonight, and you're
being very polite ABOUT IT.
>> [laughter]
>> YOU'RE BEING VERY POLITE.
BUT you haven't heard anything I've said
all night.
All he heard WAS SOMEBODY BOO BY THE
LIGHT OF THE MOON AND THE RIVER FLOW
SATURDAY.
ALL THAT SINGING FROM THE PAST TIMES,
[\h__\h]
>> [laughter]
>> He's going to be like, "What did you do
last night?" He was like, "I think I saw
Lizzo. I don't
>> [laughter]
>> She had a new song about squirting in
the apocalypse.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm a comic by the way. I'm a great
comic.